mobileburn.com 2004-09-17

# Review: Privacy Policy (MobileBurn)

| 

## Privacy Policy 

## MobileBurn.com Privacy Statement

**Use of personal information**

Currently the collection of personal information on MobileBurn.com is limited to information that is indicated by voluntary participation in our voting polls. Such information is captured only on an aggregate basis and is not associated with any mark or ID that links it back to the voting poll participant.

In the future, MobileBurn.com may collect personal information in the form of sponsored contests or surveys. If and when such an event occurs, we will state very clearly up front whether any of the information to be collected will be supplied to the event sponsor or any other party associated with MobileBurn.com. At that time the user may choose on their own if they are willing to participate.

Users that choose to participate in our forums site, Forums.MobileBurn.Com, will be asked to provide a minimum of information that includes: a chosen user name, a password, a valid email address. The email address is used to verify the user of the Forums.MobileBurn.com account and to provide notifications of received forum private messages or changes in discussion threads that the user has chosen to subscribe to. We may, from time to time, make use of that email address to contact you in the event of a problem or a question. All other information that is supplied by the user at registration is optional. We reserve the right to make use of the information you supply on an aggregate basis, but will not use the information in a way that links it to your identity. For example, we may make use of your age to determine that 35% of our users are within the ages of 25 to 30, but we will not ever supply data that states that you, John User, are 28 years old.

**Use of email addresses**

MobileBurn.com and Forums.MobileBurn.com receive many emails from our users by way of user feedback. We will never sell a list of the collected addresses and will not use them for seeding any future mailing lists that we may or may not create. We believe in opt-in for all mailing lists. Opt-out lists seeded with your email address without your permission is plainly wrong. We feel very strongly about this.

**Use of cookies**

The MobileBurn.com and Forums.MobileBurn.com sites make use of cookies for the purposes of enabling our web applications to run. Without the use of cookies we would not be able to tell what voting polls you have already participated in, or what messages on the forums you have already read. Additionally, we use the cookies to help us better track website usage. Cookies will identify you as a unique but unknown individual, and will allows us to see what pages you visit in a browsing session. This does not tell our servers who you are, or where you are located, but merely allows our web reports to calculate the number of unique individuals that visit our sites or read a particular story in a given period of time. This demographic information is used by us when dealing with potential advertisers so that we can accurately estimate how many people would potentially see an advertisement that was displayed on our site. Nothing more. It does not link you as an individual to your browsing habits, though we can not assure you that ads on our sites served by third party ad serving sites that use cookies do not behave this way.

MobileBurn.com reserves the right to change, modify, or update this statement at any time without notice.
